By using our site, you acknowledge that you have read and understand our [Privacy Policy](https://minecraft-server.net/page/privacy/) and our [Terms of Service](https://minecraft-server.net/page/terms/).

Accept Cookies and Terms

Filter

Order By Votes Popular Online Newest Recently Updated

Gamemode All Adventure Bedwars Bukkit Call of Duty Cops and Robbers Cracked Creative Curse Custom Enchants Economy Eggwars Faction Feed the Beast GTA Greifing HCF Hunger Games KitPVP MCMMO Minigames Network OP PVP OP Prison PVE PVP Parkour Pixelmon Prison Raiding Roleplay Skyblock Skygrid Skywars Survival Survival Games TNT Wars Technic Launcher Towny Vanilla Whitelist

Server Language All Afghanistan Albania Algeria American Samoa Andorra Angola Anguilla Antarctica Antigua and Barbuda Argentina Armenia Aruba Australia Austria Azerbaijan Bahamas Bahrain Bangladesh Barbados Belarus Belgium Belize Benin Bermuda Bhutan Bolivia Bosnia and Herzegovina Botswana Bouvet Island Brazil British Antarctic Territory British Indian Ocean Territory British Virgin Islands Brunei Bulgaria Burkina Faso Burundi Cambodia Cameroon Canada Cape Verde Cayman Islands Central African Republic Chad Chile China Christmas Island Cocos \[Keeling\] Islands Colombia Comoros Congo - Brazzaville Congo - Kinshasa Cook Islands Costa Rica Croatia Cuba Cyprus Czech Republic Côte d’Ivoire Denmark Djibouti Dominica Dominican Republic Ecuador Egypt El Salvador Equatorial Guinea Eritrea Estonia Ethiopia Falkland Islands Faroe Islands Fiji Finland France French Guiana French Polynesia French Southern Territories French Southern and Antarctic Territories Gabon Gambia Georgia Germany Ghana Gibraltar Greece Greenland Grenada Guadeloupe Guam Guatemala Guernsey Guinea Guinea-Bissau Guyana Haiti Heard Island and McDonald Islands Honduras Hong Kong SAR China Hungary Iceland India Indonesia Iran Iraq Ireland Israel Italy Jamaica Japan Jordan Kazakhstan Kenya Kiribati Kuwait Kyrgyzstan Laos Latvia Lebanon Lesotho Liberia Libya Liechtenstein Lithuania Luxembourg Macau SAR China Macedonia Madagascar Malawi Malaysia Maldives Mali Malta Marshall Islands Martinique Mauritania Mauritius Mayotte Mexico Micronesia Moldova Monaco Mongolia Montenegro Montserrat Morocco Mozambique Myanmar \[Burma\] Namibia Nauru Nepal Netherlands Netherlands Antilles New Caledonia New Zealand Nicaragua Niger Nigeria Niue Norfolk Island North Korea Northern Mariana Islands Norway Oman Pakistan Palau Palestinian Territories Panama Papua New Guinea Paraguay Peru Philippines Pitcairn Islands Poland Portugal Puerto Rico Qatar Romania Russia Rwanda Réunion Saint Helena Saint Kitts and Nevis Saint Lucia Saint Pierre and Miquelon Saint Vincent and the Grenadines Samoa San Marino Saudi Arabia Senegal Serbia Serbia and Montenegro Seychelles Sierra Leone Singapore Slovakia Slovenia Solomon Islands Somalia South Africa South Georgia and the South Sandwich Islands South Korea Spain Sri Lanka Sudan Suriname Svalbard and Jan Mayen Swaziland Sweden Switzerland Syria São Tomé and Príncipe Taiwan Tajikistan Tanzania Thailand Timor-Leste Togo Tokelau Tonga Trinidad and Tobago Tunisia Turkey Turkmenistan Turks and Caicos Islands Tuvalu U.S. Minor Outlying Islands U.S. Virgin Islands Uganda Ukraine United Arab Emirates United Kingdom United States Uruguay Uzbekistan Vanuatu Vatican City Venezuela Vietnam Wallis and Futuna Western Sahara Yemen Zambia Zimbabwe Åland Islands

Version All 1.21.4 1.21.3 1.21.2 1.21.1 1.21 1.20.6 1.20.5 1.20.4 1.20.3 1.20.2 1.20.1 1.20 1.19.4 1.19.3 1.19.2 1.19.1 1.19 1.18.2 1.18.1 1.18 1.17.1 1.17 1.16.5 1.16.4 1.16.3 1.16.2 1.16.1 1.16 1.15.2 1.15.1 1.15 1.14.4 1.14.3 1.14.2 1.14.1 1.14 1.13.2 1.13.1 1.13 1.12.2 1.12.1 1.12 1.11.2 1.11.1 1.11 1.10.2 1.10.1 1.10 1.9.4 1.9.3 1.9.2 1.9.1 1.9 1.8.9 1.8.8 1.8.7 1.8.6 1.8.5 1.8.4 1.8.3 1.8.2 1.8.1 1.8 1.7.10 1.7.9 1.7.8 1.7.7 1.7.6 1.7.5 1.7.4 1.7.3 1.7.2 1.6.4 1.6.2 1.6.1 1.5.2 1.5.1 1.4.7 1.4.6 1.4.5 1.4.4 1.4.2 1.3.2 1.3.1 1.2.5 1.2.4 1.2.3 1.2.2 1.2.1 1.1 1.0 1.21.4-rc3 1.21.4-rc2 1.21.4-rc1 1.21.4-pre3 1.21.4-pre2 1.21.4-pre1 24w46a 24w45a 24w44a 1.21.2-rc2 1.21.2-rc1 1.21.2-pre5 1.21.2-pre4 1.21.2-pre3 1.21.2-pre2 1.21.2-pre1 24w40a 24w39a 24w38a 24w37a 24w36a 24w35a 24w34a 24w33a 1.21.1-rc1 1.21-rc1 1.21-pre4 1.21-pre3 1.21-pre2 1.21-pre1 24w21b 24w21a 24w20a 24w19b 24w19a 24w18a 1.20.6-rc1 1.20.5-rc3 1.20.5-rc2 1.20.5-rc1 1.20.5-pre4 1.20.5-pre3 1.20.5-pre2 1.20.5-pre1 24w14a 24w14potato 24w13a 24w12a 24w11a 24w10a 24w09a 24w07a 24w06a 24w05b 24w05a 24w04a 24w03b 24w03a 23w51b 23w51a 1.20.4-rc1 1.20.3-rc1 1.20.3-pre4 1.20.3-pre3 1.20.3-pre2 1.20.3-pre1 23w46a 23w45a 23w44a 23w43b 23w43a 23w42a 23w41a 23w40a 1.20.2-rc2 1.20.2-rc1 1.20.2-pre4 1.20.2-pre3 1.20.2-pre2 1.20.2-pre1 23w35a 23w33a 23w32a 23w31a 1.20.1-rc1 1.20-rc1 1.20-pre7 1.20-pre6 1.20-pre5 1.20-pre4 1.20-pre3 1.20-pre2 1.20-pre1 23w18a 23w17a 23w16a 23w14a 23w13a\_or\_b 23w13a 23w12a 1.19.4-rc3 1.19.4-rc2 1.19.4-rc1 1.19.4-pre4 1.19.4-pre3 1.19.4-pre2 1.19.4-pre1 23w07a 23w06a 23w05a 23w04a 23w03a 1.19.3-rc3 1.19.3-rc2 1.19.3-rc1 1.19.3-pre3 1.19.3-pre2 1.19.3-pre1 22w46a 22w45a 22w44a 22w43a 22w42a 1.19.2-rc2 1.19.2-rc1 1.19.1-rc3 1.19.1-rc2 1.19.1-pre6 1.19.1-pre5 1.19.1-pre4 1.19.1-pre3 1.19.1-pre2 1.19.1-rc1 1.19.1-pre1 22w24a 1.19-rc2 1.19-rc1 1.19-pre5 1.19-pre4 1.19-pre3 1.19-pre2 1.19-pre1 22w19a 22w18a 22w17a 22w16b 22w16a 22w15a 22w14a 22w13oneblockatatime 22w13a 22w12a 22w11a 1.18.2-rc1 1.18.2-pre3 1.18.2-pre2 1.18.2-pre1 22w07a 22w06a 22w05a 22w03a 1.18.1-rc3 1.18.1-rc2 1.18.1-rc1 1.18.1-pre1 1.18-rc4 1.18-rc3 1.18-rc2 1.18-rc1 1.18-pre8 1.18-pre7 1.18-pre6 1.18-pre5 1.18-pre4 1.18-pre3 1.18-pre2 1.18-pre1 21w44a 21w43a 21w42a 21w41a 21w40a 21w39a 21w38a 21w37a 1.17.1-rc2 1.17.1-rc1 1.17.1-pre3 1.17.1-pre2 1.17.1-pre1 1.17-rc2 1.17-rc1 1.17-pre5 1.17-pre4 1.17-pre3 1.17-pre2 1.17-pre1 21w20a 21w19a 21w18a 21w17a 21w16a 21w15a 21w14a 21w13a 21w11a 21w10a 21w08b 21w08a 21w07a 21w06a 21w05b 21w05a 21w03a 1.16.5-rc1 20w51a 20w49a 20w48a 20w46a 20w45a 1.16.4-rc1 1.16.4-pre2 1.16.4-pre1 1.16.3-rc1 1.16.2-rc2 1.16.2-rc1 1.16.2-pre3 1.16.2-pre2 1.16.2-pre1 20w30a 20w29a 20w28a 20w27a 1.16-rc1 1.16-pre8 1.16-pre7 1.16-pre6 1.16-pre5 1.16-pre4 1.16-pre3 1.16-pre2 1.16-pre1 20w22a 20w21a 20w20b 20w20a 20w19a 20w18a 20w17a 20w16a 20w15a 20w14a 20w14infinite 20w13b 20w13a 20w12a 20w11a 20w10a 20w09a 20w08a 20w07a 20w06a 1.15.2-pre2 1.15.2-pre1 1.15.1-pre1 1.15-pre7 1.15-pre6 1.15-pre5 1.15-pre4 1.15-pre3 1.15-pre2 1.15-pre1 19w46b 19w46a 19w45b 19w45a 19w44a 19w42a 19w41a 19w40a 19w39a 19w38b 19w38a 19w37a 19w36a 19w35a 19w34a 1.14.4-pre7 1.14.4-pre6 1.14.4-pre5 1.14.4-pre4 1.14.4-pre3 1.14.4-pre2 1.14.4-pre1 1.14.3-pre4 1.14.3-pre3 1.14.3-pre2 1.14.3-pre1 1.14.2 Pre-Release 4 1.14.2 Pre-Release 3 1.14.2 Pre-Release 2 1.14.2 Pre-Release 1 1.14.1 Pre-Release 2 1.14.1 Pre-Release 1 1.14 Pre-Release 5 1.14 Pre-Release 4 1.14 Pre-Release 3 1.14 Pre-Release 2 1.14 Pre-Release 1 19w14b 19w14a 3D Shareware v1.34 19w13b 19w13a 19w12b 19w12a 19w11b 19w11a 19w09a 19w08b 19w08a 19w07a 19w06a 19w05a 19w04b 19w04a 19w03c 19w03b 19w03a 19w02a 18w50a 18w49a 18w48b 18w48a 18w47b 18w47a 18w46a 18w45a 18w44a 18w43c 18w43b 18w43a 1.13.2-pre2 1.13.2-pre1 1.13.1-pre2 1.13.1-pre1 18w33a 18w32a 18w31a 18w30b 18w30a 1.13-pre10 1.13-pre9 1.13-pre8 1.13-pre7 1.13-pre6 1.13-pre5 1.13-pre4 1.13-pre3 1.13-pre2 1.13-pre1 18w22c 18w22b 18w22a 18w21b 18w21a 18w20c 18w20b 18w20a 18w19b 18w19a 18w16a 18w15a 18w14b 18w14a 18w11a 18w10d 18w10c 18w10b 18w10a 18w09a 18w08b 18w08a 18w07c 18w07b 18w07a 18w06a 18w05a 18w03b 18w03a 18w02a 18w01a 17w50a 17w49b 17w49a 17w48a 17w47b 17w47a 17w46a 17w45b 17w45a 17w43b 17w43a 1.12.2-pre2 1.12.2-pre1 1.12.1-pre1 17w31a 1.12-pre7 1.12-pre6 1.12-pre5 1.12-pre4 1.12-pre3 1.12-pre2 1.12-pre1 17w18b 17w18a 17w17b 17w17a 17w16b 17w16a 17w15a 17w14a 17w13b 17w13a 17w06a 16w50a 1.11-pre1 16w44a 16w43a 16w42a 16w41a 16w40a 16w39c 16w39b 16w39a 16w38a 16w36a 16w35a 16w33a 16w32b 16w32a 1.10-pre2 1.10-pre1 16w21b 16w21a 16w20a 1.9.3-pre3 1.9.3-pre2 1.9.3-pre1 16w15b 16w15a 16w14a 1.RV-Pre1 1.9.1-pre3 1.9.1-pre2 1.9.1-pre1 1.9-pre4 1.9-pre3 1.9-pre2 1.9-pre1 16w07b 16w07a 16w06a 16w05b 16w05a 16w04a 16w03a 16w02a 15w51b 15w51a 15w50a 15w49b 15w49a 15w47c 15w47b 15w47a 15w46a 15w45a 15w44b 15w44a 15w43c 15w43b 15w43a 15w42a 15w41b 15w41a 15w40b 15w40a 15w39c 15w39b 15w39a 15w38b 15w38a 15w37a 15w36d 15w36c 15w36b 15w36a 15w35e 15w35d 15w35c 15w35b 15w35a 15w34d 15w34c 15w34b 15w34a 15w33c 15w33b 15w33a 15w32c 15w32b 15w32a 15w31c 15w31b 15w31a 15w14a 1.8.2-pre7 1.8.2-pre6 1.8.2-pre5 1.8.2-pre4 1.8.2-pre3 1.8.2-pre2 1.8.2-pre1 1.8.1-pre5 1.8.1-pre4 1.8.1-pre3 1.8.1-pre2 1.8.1-pre1 1.8-pre3 1.8-pre2 1.8-pre1 14w34d 14w34c 14w34b 14w34a 14w33c 14w33b 14w33a 14w32d 14w32c 14w32b 14w32a 14w31a 14w30c 14w30b 14w30a 14w29b 14w29a 14w28b 14w28a 14w27b 14w27a 14w26c 14w26b 14w26a 14w25b 14w25a 14w21b 14w21a 14w20b 14w20a 1.7.10-pre4 1.7.10-pre3 1.7.10-pre2 1.7.10-pre1 14w19a 14w18b 14w18a 14w17a 14w11b 14w11a 1.7.6-pre2 1.7.6-pre1 14w10c 14w10b 14w10a 14w08a 14w07a 14w06b 14w06a 14w05b 14w05a 14w04b 14w04a 14w03b 14w03a 14w02c 14w02b 14w02a 13w49a 13w48b 13w48a 13w47e 13w47d 13w47c 13w47b 13w47a 1.7.1 1.7 13w43a 13w42b 13w42a 13w41b 13w41a 13w39b 13w39a 13w38c 13w38b 13w38a 13w37b 1.6.3 13w37a 13w36b 13w36a 1.6 13w26a 13w25c 13w25b 13w25a 13w24b 13w24a 13w23b 13w23a 13w22a 13w21b 13w21a 13w19a 13w18c 13w18b 13w18a 13w17a 13w16b 13w16a 1.5 1.4.3 1.4.1 1.4 1.3

Active Servers

[

Mistylands Survival Est.2010](https://minecraft-server.net/details/mistylands/ "Mistylands Survival Est.2010")[

MC.PROJECTS.GG TÜRK SURVIVAL SUNUCU - Mevsimler/Kanli Ay/Unvanlar/AntiXray/PvP - 1.20.4](https://minecraft-server.net/details/projectsurvival/ "MC.PROJECTS.GG TÜRK SURVIVAL SUNUCU - Mevsimler/Kanli Ay/Unvanlar/AntiXray/PvP - 1.20.4")[

KoalaServers | 1.21, Survival, Creative, Land Claiming, Anti-Grief, Economy, Ranks, Player Shops, McMMO, Jobs!](https://minecraft-server.net/details/KoalaServers/ "KoalaServers | 1.21, Survival, Creative, Land Claiming, Anti-Grief, Economy, Ranks, Player Shops, McMMO, Jobs!")[

Skyblock Anarchy](https://minecraft-server.net/details/SkyblockAnarchy/ "Skyblock Anarchy")[

~~ MetaUnion ~~ \[Friendly Community, No Pay2Win, RPG Survival, Creative\]](https://minecraft-server.net/details/Folas1337/ "~~ MetaUnion ~~ [Friendly Community, No Pay2Win, RPG Survival, Creative]")

1. [Minecraft Servers](https://minecraft-server.net/)
2. Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

**What information do we collect?**  
  
We collect information from you when you register on http://minecraft-server.net, place an order and/or when you vote for a minecraft server on this web site.

When registering on http://minecraft-server.net, as appropriate, you will be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit http://minecraft-server.net anonymously. When placing an order we will require your name and address. For European costumers that represent a company we may also require a valid Business name, Registration number and VAT before placing an order. When voting for a minecraft server on http://minecraft-server.net we may collect your entered minecraft username (for Votifer purposes) and IP address to prevent double-voting and also to validate your vote.  
  
**What do we use your information for?**  
  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:  
• To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs).  
• To improve Minecraft-Server.net (we continually strive to improve http://minecraft-server.net offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).  
• To prevent booting or any kind of ways to cheat the voting system.  
• To improve our customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).  
• To process transactions (such as payments for additional services).  
• At the point when an end-user wishes to make a payment, his registration details may be passed to Paymentwall that provides payment processing services, in order for Paymentwall to better protect service and end-users from unauthorized payments

• Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.

• To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature.  
• To send periodic emails (the email address you provide for order processing, will only be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order).

**How do we protect your information?**  
  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information. We take reasonable steps to secure your personally identifiable information against unauthorized access or disclosure. Information we collect may be stored or processed on computers located in any country where we do business. Special situations may require disclosure of your data.  
  
**Do we use cookies?**  
  
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies only to save your login preferences for future visits and to prevent booting and voting cheats. If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options.

Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website and/or minecraft server. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet. We at http://minecraft-server.net use tools such as (but not limited too) Google Analytics, Google Webmasters and Google Adsense to help improve the experience and maintain our service.

Users may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie for interest-based advertising by visiting Ads Settings. (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest based advertising by visiting [aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/).)

http://minecraft-server.net (and any sub domains) uses a third party protection service offered by Cloudflare. This service may place cookies on the browsers in order to track malicious visitors, to reduce the chance of blocking legitimate users, and to provide customized services. The \_\_cfduid cookie by Cloudflare is used to override any security restrictions based on the IP address the visitor is coming from. If you do not want CloudFlare to use cookies, you can disable them within your browser.  

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**  
  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating http://minecraft-server.net, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety.  

**Third party links**  
  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on http://minecraft-server.net. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.  
  
**Online Privacy Policy Only**  
  
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through http://minecraft-server.net and not to information collected offline.  
  
**Your Consent**  
  
By using and accessing http://minecraft-server.net website, you consent to our privacy policy.  
  
Our privacy policy may change from time to time. If we make any material changes to our policies, we will place a prominent notice on http://minecraft-server.net or application. If the change materially affects registered users, we will send a notice to you by email, notification or text.  
If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policies, please [Contact Us](https://minecraft-server.net/contact/)

**Last Edit : 19th Feburary 2019  
**

### Language Selector

Select Language

EnglishDeutsch

Set

 Dark Mode

#### Social Links

#### Site Links

© Minecraft-Server.net 2024. All rights reserved. 'Minecraft' is a property of [Mojang](https://www.mojang.com/). You can buy [Minecraft here](https://www.minecraft.net/). 7 queries, time: 0.06287 - Created by [Debaucus](https://debauc.us/)
